<resources>
    <string name="app_name">readkami beta</string>
    <string name="Journal1">The Journal of Economic and Enterprise Studies (JEES) is dedicated to establishing a vibrant exchange platform for scholars, researchers, and practitioners engaged in the fields of economics and enterprise, particularly within the Southeast Asian context with a special emphasis on the Philippines. Our primary objective is to foster a dynamic, mutually beneficial dialogue between contributors and the wider community of academics, policymakers, and industry professionals who benefit from this research.

--Core Focus--

JEES is committed to disseminating cutting-edge research findings and advancing scientific knowledge in the realms of economics and enterprise. Our focus encompasses a range of critical areas:

1. Economic Development and Policy: Delving into the strategies, outcomes, and implications of economic policies in Southeast Asia, with an emphasis on sustainable and inclusive growth.
2. Entrepreneurship and Innovation: Exploring the vibrant world of startups, innovation strategies, and their impact on regional economies.
3. International Trade and Finance: Analyzing the complexities of global trade, financial markets, and economic integration from a Southeast Asian perspective.
4. Sustainable Business and Corporate Responsibility: Investigating the intersection of business practices with environmental sustainability and social responsibility.
5. Agricultural Economics: Examining the sector\'s influence on regional economies, rural development, and policy-making.
6. Behavioral Economics and Consumer Behavior: Unraveling the psychological aspects of economic decision-making in the digital era.
7. Human Resource Management and Organizational Behavior: Studying the strategies for workforce development and organizational effectiveness in diverse cultural settings.
8. Public Sector Economics and Policy Analysis: Assessing the impact of governmental actions in economic contexts.
9. Urban and Regional Economics: Focusing on urbanization, regional development, and spatial economic dynamics.
10. Financial Technology and Digital Economy: Investigating the transformative role of digital innovations in economics and business.</string>

    <string-array name="book_title">
        <item>Um Digos Research Journal</item>
        <item>Gomanan</item>
        <item>The Pendulum</item>
        <item>La Ricerca</item>
        <item>Tinubhan</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="book_subtitle">
        <item>About the Journal</item>
        <item>About the Journal</item>
        <item>About the Journal</item>
        <item>About the Journal</item>
        <item>About the Journal</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>